Hello, I'm Jeyhun Ashurbayov

Who is advanced Full-Stack Web Developer with 5 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive websites. Innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users. Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with attractive, user-friendly websites.

Technical Skills

Front-end:

- HTML5, CSS3
- JavaScript (ES2015 / ES6)
- React, Redux, Redux-Saga, AngularJS, jQuery
- Babel, Webpack, Gulp, Grunt
- Bootstrap, Semantic UI, MaterializeCSS, Angular Material

Back-end:

- NodeJs (Express.Js, Socket.lo)
- PHP (Yii2, Slim)
- REST services
- APNS, GCM, Facebook SDK/API, Braintree API, Payoneer Escrow API...

Software Design:

- Design Patterns, OOP, Functional programming (Ramda, Lodash)
- Continuous Integration / Delivery / Deployment (*Travis Cl, CodeShip*)
- Test/Behavior Driven Development (Karma, Jasmine, Mocha, Jest, Chai, Enzyme)

DataBases:

- MySql
- MongoDB

Mobile Application Development:

- Hybrid (Ionic 1, Ionic 2, Cordova)
- iOS (Swift 3) non commercial

Other Tools:

- GitHub, Bitbucket
- AWS (EC2, Route 53, S3, CodeDeploy)
- Photoshop / Sketch / Zeplin
- Cloud9

Experience

MAY 2017 - PRESENT | Remote

Gothru.co - Web Developer

- Continuously providing assistance in both front and back part of application
- Created virtual panorama tours in use of Three.js, Krpano, Angular 4 and Google StreetView API
- Made REST API for 3rd-party applications on Node.js / Express.js

JULY 2016 - MARCH 2018

Zupamart.com / Scrapo.co - Web Developer

- Integrating real-time part of application by using NodeJs, ExpressJs and Socket.io
- Perform website maintenance and enhancements
- Providing REST services to the mobile application developers using Yii2 framework

JULY 2013 - JANUARY 2015

Encoder - Web developer

- Converted Photoshop layouts to web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Integrated Converted Photoshop layouts with my own CMS and MVC framework in PHP

MAY 2012 - APRIL 2013

WebCity - Web developer

- Translated designs to front-end code, estimated time and costs, and determined developer requirements and specifications.
- Updated and streamlined existing code to improve website performance

Education

SEPTEMBER 2011 - MAY 2015

Baku State University - Bachelor

Faculty of Applied Mathematics and Cybernetics - Computer Science. Entrance score is 590 out of 700.

Contact Details

Location: Baku, Azerbaijan
Phone: (994) 55-631-09-43
Email: c.ashurbeyli@gmail.com
Skype: ceyhun.ashurbeyli
Website: http://jeyhun.info

Social: GitHub | LinkedIn | StackOverflow